Fight Another Day is a action film directed by James Mark.
Follows a tough cop, who after being transported to a dystopian future, must
enter a deadly combat tournament to be able to return to his past.
Duke, played by Jim Belushi.
Fischer, played by Martin Kove.
Ryan Taylor, played by Eric Johnson.
Gerrard, played by Ennis Esmer.
Barbarian, played by Chuck Liddell.
Aztec, played by Ken Kilpatrick.
Fight Another Day is a 2024 Canadian science fiction action film
directed by James Mark, written by James Mark and Matthew K.
It stars Eric Johnson, Martin Kove, Christina Ochoa, and  Jim Belushi.
The plot follows officer Ryan Taylor who is plucked from the moment of his death and transported, with other combatants pulled from across
history, to a dystopian future where they must fight to the death for entertainment on the titular television show Fight Another Day.